My name is Oliver Queen.
我叫Oliver Queen
After five years on a hellish island,
經過島上的五年煉獄生活
I have come home with only one goal...
我回家只有一個目的
to save my city.
拯救我的城市
But to do so,I can't be the killer I once was.
我不能再像以前一樣成為殺手
To honor my friend's memory,I must be someone else.
為祭奠我的朋友 我必須扮成某人
I must be something else.
我必須掩蓋身份
Previously on "Arrow"...
綠箭俠 前情提要
This one's no longer of use to us.
這人對我們已經沒用了
Wait.He could still be useful.
等等 他還有用
She's right.
她說得沒錯
Once we get rid of his friends,we'll need him to lead us to the grave.
我們把他的朋友解決後 需要讓他帶我們去墓地
You're going back to the island.
你準備好回島吧
Look,you already lost your dad.
你已經失去了父親
Your mom,she's still here.
可你母親還活著
And I'm sure she'd love to see you.
我相信她很想見你
I'm not going to that prison.
我不會去監獄的
It's the only way I know how to hurt her.
我知道這樣會傷害她
And I want to hate you.
我很想恨你
But I can't.
但我不能
I didn't think that there were secrets kept between us.
我不覺得我們之間有秘密
Mom...what are you hiding?
媽 你在隱瞞什麼
My name is Moira Dearden Queen.
我是Moira Dearden Queen
I am the acting CEO of Queen Consolidated.
現任Queen集團CEO
And,God forgive me,I have failed this city.
上帝 請原諒我 我辜負了這座城市
I have been complicit in an undertaking with one horrible purpose...
我參與共謀了一場可怕目的的罪行
to destroy the Glades and everyone in it.
摧毀林中空地和裡面的每個人
If you reside in the Glades,please,you need to get out now.
如果你住在林中空地 請馬上離開
Your lives and the lives of your children depend on it.
你和你孩子們的命運取決於此刻
Please.
請求大家
Warden says we got to evacuate.
Warden叫我們撤了
Help me get these out of here.
幫我這些帶出去
What about the inmates?
那些囚犯怎麼辦
Leave 'em.
讓他們去
Over here,let me out.
這裡 讓我出去
No.Give me the keys!
不行 給我鑰匙
No,no,too violent.Too Sloppy,too stupid.
不行 太暴力 太邋遢 太愚蠢
Too...ambitious.
野心太大
You.
你
I love your work.
我喜歡你的工作
Big future.
有前途
Hey,be careful.
小心點
There's liable to be aftershocks.
還會有餘震
Oh,I'm counting on it.
就靠它了
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Proudly Presents
-=伊甸園美劇 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸園字幕站 http://ytet.org=- 榮譽出品 本字幕僅供學習交流，嚴禁用於商業途徑
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com/bbs=-Sync: YTET-收音机头
-=YTET-伊甸園字幕組=- 翻譯: 看糖 DB 佐佐木 禾希飯 Ducky 校對: Andrea∞Quinn 時間軸: YTET-收音機頭
ARROW Season2Episode 02
綠箭俠 第二季 第七集
Mr.Queen,what are your mother's chances?
Queen先生 你母親勝訴的幾率有多大
Is she on suicide watch?
她有被自殺監視嗎
Mr.Queen,can you give us any comment?
Queen先生 能說點什麼嗎
It's not fair.
這不公平
They're not the ones on trial.
又不是審訊他們
That won't stop Jean Loring from using them as props to drum up sympathy.
那也不會阻止Jean Loring 利用他們作為鼓動同情的道具
You don't seem overly concerned.
你好像一點都不關心
She confessed to being an accomplice on live television.
她被電視直播承認是同謀
Also sad that Malcolm Merlyn coerced here.
但也說了是被Malcolm Merlyn脅迫的
You have something,don't you?
你打著如意算盤吧
I thought I was your co-counsel,Adam.
我以為我是你的合作律師 Adam
If you're holding a trump card,don't you think maybe you should share it with me?
如果你還有張王牌 不覺得該告訴我嗎
It's going to be a good trial.
這會是場精彩的審訊
Come on,let's get inside.
走吧 我們進去
You don't have to do this.
你沒必要這樣
Ivo says we do.
Ivo說需要
Your friends are a danger to his men.
你朋友對他們不利
Go.Quick and quiet.
走 迅速不要出聲
Slade!Shado!Run!
Slade Shado 快跑
There's no one here.
裡面沒人
They must have moved on from their position.
他們肯定轉移地點了
Chargers are placed.Here's the detonator.
電池裝好了 這是引爆器
Make sure they have no place to return to.
確保他們無處可逃
Go.
去
And you.
你
Now you're going to take us to the graves.
帶我們去墓地
Let's go.Get him up.
走 把他拉起來
Let's get clear.
我們撤
Did you find the detonator?
找到引爆器了嗎
Yes.
找到了
We were lucky.
我們比較幸運
I was lucky.
是我幸運
You were good.
你很棒
Either way...
不管如何
They have Oliver.
Oliver在他們手上
I'm going after him.
我去找他
Not alone.
我也去
You can barely walk.
你都走不了路
All the more reason not to stay here.
就不想呆在這
Give them another chance at blowing me up.
再他們次機會炸了我
Are you two ok?
你們倆沒事吧
I should be asking you that question.
該我問你吧
I'll be fine.
我沒事
You look like you have the flu.
你好像感冒了
If that's true,I shouldn't have wasted my time getting vaccinated.
感冒的話我該去打疫苗了
Diggle,whatever it is,just go home.
Diggle 不管怎麼回事 你回家吧
Oliver,listen,I can take care of things.
Oliver 我能處理好
No,we'll be fine,all right?
不行 我們沒事的
Go rest.And don't make me call a cop.
回去休息 別讓我叫警察
There are a few of them around here.
這有不少呢
...have been complicit in an undertaking with one horrible purpose...
...參與共謀了一場可怕目的的罪行
to destroy the Glades and everyone in it.
摧毀林中空地和裡面的每個人
And it worked.
目的達到了
The Glades were destroyed.
林中空地被摧毀了
Homes and lives were lost.
家園和生命都沒有了
All because of her actions.
都是因為她
True,she had second thoughts; Remorse which compelled her to deliver this statement.
沒錯 她的確猶豫過 罪惡感使她發表了這樣的陳述
But on behalf of the 503 lives that were extinguished that day,
但代表那天死去的503條人命
I say,Moira Queen,your remorse comes too late.
我只能說 Moira Queen 你懺悔的太晚了
For the last five years,under the threat for my life and the lives of my family...
過去五年 在我和我家人的生命 受到威脅的情況下...
Why wouldn't those threats silence her?
這些威脅不該讓她沉默嗎
Why wouldn't Moira Queen be terrified?
Moira Queen不該害怕嗎
Malcolm Merlyn killed her first husband,abducted her second.
Malcolm Merlyn殺了她的第一任丈夫 又綁架了第二任
Why wouldn't she be in fear for her life?
她不該為她自己和孩子們膽戰心驚嗎
What would you do?
換做是你會怎麼做
If it were your children in the crosshairs of a mad man's rage?
如果是你的孩子被一個瘋男人瞄準
S.T.A.R.Lab's particle accelerator will be turned on right on schedule.
STAR實驗室的粒子加速器將按時啟動
In other news,we have just received word
其他新聞 收到消息稱Moira Queen
that both sides have now completed their opening statements in the Moira Queen trial.
一案原被告都已發表陳述完畢
Don't take this the wrong way,but you look disgusting.
你看上去有點噁心 別曲解我意思
Yeah,well,I don't feel great,Felicity.
是的 我感覺不舒服 Felicity
Is there a right way to take that?
有正解嗎
You should go home.
你該回家
I am going.
是準備走了
I just need to make arrangements for a replacement bodyguard.
我得安排個替補保鏢
Did you get the flu shot?
你打過流感疫苗了嗎
Personally,I never do.I know that I should.
我是不會打 雖然我知道應該要打
I just,I have this thing about needles.
我只是不太待見針
All pointy things,really.
所有尖的東西 真的
Which is ironic,considering who we work with.
諷刺的是 想到我們的合作夥伴
Yeah,it's not the flu,Felicity,it's more like...
沒錯 這不是流感 Felicity 更像是...
Dig!
Dig
Hello?
有人嗎
Are you here?
你在這兒嗎
Here...
在這兒
there...
在那兒
everywhere.
在任何地方
So.How goes our little science project?
我們的科學項目進展如何
Working like you said it would.
如你所料
How wonderful.
多棒啊
Ah,so listen.
是這樣
Doing the thing was 50,000.
幹這事兒要五萬塊
Keeping quiet about it,I'm thinking it should be 50 more.
保守這個秘密 我覺得還得加五萬塊
Oh,I want word to spread.
不過我想讓這個消息散開
It's kind of the whole objective,actually.
事實上 這是整體目標的一部分
You see my point?
懂我意思了嗎
You should know,I find post hoc negotiation...
你應該知道 我覺得時候談判
distasteful.
很討厭
Such a shame you won't get to see what your works have wrought,doctor.
只可惜你看不到自己的成就了 博士
But soon,everyone else will.
但很快 所有人都會看到
And they'll beg for it to end.
而且他們會祈求它快點結束
What the hell are you doing here?
你來這兒幹嘛
I heard you passed out.
我聽說你昏過去了
I told Felicity not to call you.
我告訴過Felicity別給你打電話
Yeah,but before that,you said "gaw" and "thud," so I didn't take it very seriously.
沒錯 但在那之前 你喊了一聲就倒下了 所以我沒把那句話當回事
She was right to call me.Diggle,you need medical attention.
她打給我是對的 Diggle 你需要就醫
He needs more than that.
他需要的不只是醫生
When Dig passed out,I sent a sample of his blood to a chemist I know at QC.
Dig昏過去時 我把他的血樣送給了集團的一名化學家
The guy owes me a favor.Long story,I fixed his parking ticket.
他欠我人情 說來話長 我幫他取消過停車罰單
Huh.I guess it's not that long.
其實也不是那麼長
Felicity.The blood sample.
Felicity 血樣
Yeah.It came back positive...
對 迷幻檢測結果
for trace amounts of Vertigo.
顯示陽性
I never used Vertigo before in my life.
我從沒用過迷幻
You were exposed to it somehow.
你肯定是接觸到了
Vertigo's in play again?
迷幻又出現了嗎
When the Count recovered from his OD on Vertigo,he was sent to Iron Heights.
伯爵迷幻吸入過量被治好後 警方把他送到了鐵山監獄
That got hit in the quake.
監獄在地震中坍塌了
He got out the same way the Doll Maker did?
他和娃娃製造者用同一方法逃出來的
And just like with the Doll Maker,
而且和娃娃製造者一樣
prison officials worked overtime to keep the lid on the escape.
警方加班加點地工作掩蓋他逃逸的消息
I know what you're thinking.
我知道你在想什麼
No,you don't.
不 你不知道
I made a choice not to put an arrow in this guy.
我當時選擇不殺他
And it was the right choice.
這是個正確的決定
There's no more killing.
不會再有殺戮
I worked this up to counteract the effects of Vertigo.
我做了這個來消除迷幻的藥效
Give it to Diggle.I...
給Diggle注射 我
I need to get back to court.
我得回法庭去
While I'm gone,just work up whatever you can
我不在的時候
and figure out how Diggle got Vertigo in his system without his knowledge.
盡一切努力查清楚Diggle是怎麼 在不知不覺的情況下沾上迷幻的
Ok.Go.
好 去吧
When was the first time you heard about this so-called Undertaking?
你第一次聽說這所謂的事業 是什麼時候
When everyone else did,when my mother gave the press conference.
跟大家一樣 在我媽開發佈會的時候
Doesn't seem like you took it too well.
你好像不是很能接受這個消息
I was surprised.
我很吃驚
Who wouldn't be?
誰不會呢
Uh,your mother was,um,immediately take into custody,
你母親當時 立刻就被逮捕了
but I assume you went down to the precinct to see her?
不過你應該去看守所看過她吧
Um,actually I didn't see her until she was moved.
其實在她轉移之前我都沒見過她
To the prison.
轉移去監獄
Do you remember when you visited her?
還記得你是什麼時候去看她的嗎
Uh,not the exact date.
記不清具體日期了
It's ok,I have the visitor log here.
沒關係 我這兒有訪客記錄
October ninth.
十月九號
Five months later.
也就是整整五個月
Why so long?
怎麼這麼久
Um,I...I...
我 我
Are you ok?
你沒事吧
An answer,please.
請回答
Why did it take you five months to visit your mother?
為什麼等了五個月之久才去看你母親
Your Honor,if I...
法官大人 請讓我
No.I want to hear this.
我 我想聽這個問題的答案
I needed time.
我需要時間
I was...
我那時
Angry.
很生氣
So angry,perhaps,that it took you five months to forgive her?
可能是太生氣了 所以你隔了五個月才去原諒她
It was complicated.
事情很複雜
No.It's very simple.
不 很簡單
You blamed your mother for what she had done.
你因為你母親的所作所為而責怪她
So why shouldn't the jury?
那麼陪審團為什麼不能
Your Honor,we have no further questions for the...witness.
法官大人 我們沒有問題詢問證人了
Adam!
Adam
Where is it?
在哪兒
Come on,where is it?!
東西在哪兒呢
The Hosen,where is it?
護身符在哪裡
- What? - The arrowhead.
- 什麼東西 - 箭頭
Every report said it was with these bodies.
所有報告都說這些屍體旁邊都有箭頭
You said you and your friends were here.
你說你和你的朋友曾在這兒
Now,where is it?
現在東西呢
Take him outside.
把他帶出去
Make him show you where his friends are hiding.
逼他告訴你他的朋友在哪兒
Take us to them.
帶我們去找他們
I don't know where they are!
我不知道他們在哪兒
Tell me,or you lose your hand.
告訴我 否則把你的手廢了
Let us suggest another option.
我們試試別的選擇
You hand the kid over to us,and we don't kill you all.
你把人交給我們 我們就留你們性命
Hey,are you ok?
你還好嗎
Don't worry about me.
別擔心我
I can take it.
我承受得了
Was that as bad as it seemed?
和看上去一樣糟糕嗎
Thea's testimony?
Thea的證詞嗎
It was a set-back.
確實有點不利
We were counting on her to... Humanize me.
我們本指望她來 告訴別人我也是人
Frankly,yes.
坦白的說 是的
And now we're going to have to go another way.
現在我們需要試試別的辦法了
No. No,I told you,I won't testify.
不 我跟你說過了 我不會出庭作證的
I know you did.
我知道你說過
But now you have to.
但你知道你必須這麼做
She's right,Mom.
她是對的 媽
Jean,can you give us a minute?
Jean 能讓我們單獨說兩句嗎
Yeah.
當然
I know what you're going to say.
我知道你要說什麼
But if I testify,it will destroy our family.
但如果我出庭作證了 那會毀了我們整個家庭
And if your lawyer's right,you don't have a choice.
如果你的律師是對的 那麼你沒有其他選擇
Mom,secrets are what put you in this situation.
媽 正是秘密讓你處於今天這困境的
Secrets and lies.
秘密和謊言
And now it is time to give the truth its day.
現在是時候說出真相了
Now,I don't want us to lose sight of the other major event in court today.
不得不提的是今天庭審中的 另外一件重要事件
Was there any indication of Adam Donner being ill?
Adam Donner發病之前有任何跡像嗎
No,there was very little warning before Mr.Donner collapsed to the ground.
沒有 Donner先生倒地前 幾乎沒有任何跡象
I've spoken to several people that were in the courtroom with me...
我與當時在法庭裡的幾個人談過了
How are you feeling?
感覺怎樣
Fine.
還好
You have a lousy poker face,Diggle.
你講大話真遜啊 Diggle
Did he take the antidote?
他服用解毒藥了嗎
Didn't work.
沒有起到作用
The Count must have futzed with his recipe.
伯爵一定改進了配方
Heard what happened with Donner at the court,and with Thea.
我聽到了庭審時Donner發生的狀況 還有Thea
How is she?
她還好嗎
Going to be fine.
她會沒事的
Your poker face isn't much better than mine,Oliver.
你比我好不到哪兒去 Oliver
Hello,Starling City.
你好 斯特林市
Felicity!
Felicity
Miss me?
想我了嗎
Many of you have noticed that you're not feeling quite like yourselves...
你們中的很多人都感到身體不適了吧
He's taken over all the local station feeds.
他控制了當地所有的信號源
Track his signal.
追蹤他的信號
Like our good assistant district attorney here.
就像我們能幹的地方助理檢察官一樣
You might recognize him from his work in the ongoing Moira Queen trial.
從正在審訊的Moira Queen案件中 你們或許已經認出他了
Hi,Adam.
你好 Adam
What do you want?
你想怎樣
I want what you want.
我想如你所願
For you to feel better.
讓你感覺舒服些
Go to hell!
去死吧
I do think you want the pain to end,and I can do that...
我確信你想擺脫疼痛 其實我可以幫忙
With Vertigo.
用迷幻藥
It's what all of your bodies crave.
這是你們身體最渴望的
Fortunately,the power of relief is right here.
幸運的是 解藥就在眼前
And all you have to do is go to your friendly neighborhood Vertigo dealer and request the cure.
你只需要找找家附近的藥販子 向他們求救
Simply supply and demand at work.
你買我賣 簡單的很
Now,tell me you want this and it's yours.
現在告訴我你需要它 我就給你
All the pain will just...
所有的痛苦就會
disappear.
煙消雲散
Say it.
張口吧
Say...
說啊
You want it.
說你想要這個
I-I...want...I want it.
我... 我想要這個
You see...
看到了吧
a simple solution.
就這麼簡單
I'm Count Vertigo,and I approve this high.
我是迷幻伯爵 保證讓你爽翻
What do we do now?
我們現在怎麼辦
We find him...
找到他
And we shut him down.
然後制服他
Where did he broadcast from?
他在哪發出直播信號的
He bounced the signal off of S.T.A.R.Lab's satellite.
他入侵了斯特林實驗室的衛星
He could have sent that transmission from Markovia.
他可以從Markovia發送信號過來的
He would want to stay local.
他肯定在本市
Scrub the footage,frame by frame if you have to.
在畫面上找 必要的話一幀幀來
There's something on here that gives us a clue to where he is.
那上面會留下線索 告訴我們他在哪的
If he dosed the whole city,why are only some people showing symptoms?
如果他給城裡所有人下了藥 為什麼只有部分人出現症狀
Maybe exposure was selective.
可能他是有選擇的
The Count contaminated something that only certain people,like you and Donner,consumed.
伯爵下藥的只是某些人 像你和Donner
A most dramatic turn.
極具戲劇性的轉變
City officials are urging calm,hoping to avoid widespread panic.
政府官員敦促大家保持冷靜 希望避免大範圍的恐慌
Deputy Mayor Levitz has...
Levitz副市長...
The Count has turned Starling into a city of junkies.
伯爵把斯特林市變成了毒城
Any leads on where he's holding ADA Donner?
他把ADA Donner關在哪 有線索了嗎
Hmm,no.
還沒有
As cold as it sounds,I've got other concerns.
無情的說一句 我還有別的擔心
Laurel?
Laurel
Adam's trial notes are very thorough.
Adam的審訊記錄很詳實
They better be.
最好是這樣
You're lead counsel now.
你現在是首席律師了
Ms.Spencer,you're the district attorney.
Spencer女士 您是地方檢察官
Yes,but you're the one that the jury knows.
是的 但陪審團更熟悉你
You'll do fine,Laurel.
你一定能做好的 Laurel
I know.
我知道
I just found Adam's trump card.
我剛發現Adam的王牌了
Sorry,I didn't hear you walk up.
抱歉 沒聽到你進來
I just want to be left alone.
我只是想一個人待會
Well,too bad that's not an option for you.
很遺憾 這可由不得你
But maybe I know something that is.
沒準我有別的辦法
Hit me.
來打我
What?
什麼
You wonder why I used to go out at night looking to throw down with bad guys.
你知道我為什麼常常夜裡出去收拾壞人嗎
Part of it was to help the city.
一是為了拯救這個城市
And the other part was to help me.
另一方面是為了幫助我自己
Getting tuned up by street thugs helped you?
被街頭暴徒教訓一頓 這能幫到你麼
Yeah,well,I gave as good as I got.
是的 我和他們奇虎相當
There we go.
好了
When I would throw a punch,I'd be so angry.
當我出拳打架時 一定是怒火中燒了
I'd feel this heat rising inside of me,in my jaw.
我感覺那種怒火發自內心 發自我的喉嚨
In my chest.
發自我的胸腔
And my fists.
還有我的拳頭
But I needed somewhere to go.
但我需要發洩
Come on.
來吧
Thea,you're angry.
Thea 你滿腔怒氣
At your mother,the D.A.,yourself,maybe.
有對你老媽的 對地方檢察官的 或許還有對你自己的
But that anger is going to chew up your insides if you don't let it out.
但如果你不發洩出來 憤怒會吞噬你的內心
I'm not going to hit you,Roy.
我不會打你的 Roy
Try.
試試吧
Try!
試試
I said hit me,right?
我是說打我
'Cause that felt like...
不是這種
that didn't really feel like anything.
不痛不癢的感覺
Better.
好多了
But keep your wrists straight.
把手腕伸直
Don't just use your arm.Put your entire body into it.
不要只是晃晃胳膊 要使出全身的力氣
Come on,again.
再來
At least let me call Lyla.
至少讓我給Lyla打個電話
All she could do is worry about me.
那只會讓她為我擔心
I found something.
我有發現
I don't see anything.
我什麼都沒看到啊
Because you have to see what Donner does.
因為你得看看Donner看到了什麼
His eye caught a reflection.
他的眼球反射出了圖像
Can you enhance?
能把圖片弄清晰些嗎
It hurts me that you feel a need to ask.
這還用問 真傷我自尊
What are those,wings?
這是什麼
It's the city seal.
這是市徽
Starling Municipal Records department.
斯特林市檔案部門
That building's been abandoned since the city went to digital.
市政辦公數字化後 這棟建築就被閒置了
Dollars to donuts,that's where  is operating out of.
可以肯定的是 那裡是伯爵的基地
Not for long.
不再是了
You shouldn't be here.
你不該來這兒的
- My attorney needs... - Moira.
- 我的律師需要... - Moira
I know I could be disbarred for speaking with you,but this isn't something for lawyers.
我知道和你交談可能會被取消律師資格 但我不是為公事而來
This is a family matter.
是為了家事
Jean told me she's calling you to the stand tomorrow.
Jean說她明天會讓你出庭作證
Yes.
是的
You can't testify.
你不能作證
Well.
什麼
The fact that you don't want me to,Laurel,is a good indication that I should.
Laurel 你不想讓我出庭 反而說明我應該出庭
If you take the stand,I'll have to cross examine you,
如果你出庭 我就必須質詢你
and I'll have to do it to the best of my ability.
而且我會打破沙鍋問到底
- Yes,I understand. - No,I don't think you do.
- 我明白 - 不 你沒明白
Forget about what this will do to Oliver and Thea.
暫且不提這對Oliver和Thea的影響
It also could undermine your entire case.
它會對你整個案件有不利影響
So,Moira,please.
所以 Moira 拜託你
Please.Don't make me use this.
拜託 別逼我用這個
Everything is at stake for you.
目前一切對於你來說都事關緊要
And I don't want to be the one to take it all away.
我不想讓你萬劫不復
Faster,please.
快點
Faster!
抓緊點
We have a city full of customers.
這城市裡到處都是我們的客戶
And I mean this literally.
一點都不誇張
I'm afraid my production apparatus is a little over-taxed with the increased demand.
我擔心我的生產設備隨著需求量的增長 要超負荷運行了
I can live with it,though.
但我可以應付
I can't say the city can.
可是這城市等不了
Go.
快走
Be still,my heart.
保持冷靜
Step away from them.
離他們遠點
Yes,I've heard you've developed an allergy to killing.
我聽說你已經厭倦殺戮了
Do it!
照我說的做
Or what?
不然呢
You'll kill me?
你會殺了我嗎
You're really on the no killing wagon?
你真的不再殺人了嗎
Shame.
真可惜
Really letting one of life's true pleasures pass you by.
那你的人生就失去了真正的樂趣
But you said you didn't want to testify.
你說過你不想出庭作證的
But you have to.
但你不得不
- Because of me. - No.
- 因為我 - 不是
You have to do damage control.
你必須把損失降到最小
None of this is your fault.
這都不是你的錯
We're here because of what I did.
現在這一切是因為我的過錯
Now,you both know the truth,but you don't know all of it.
你們已經知道了真相 但那不是全部
Laurel does.
Laurel全部知道了
What does she have?
她知道什麼了
You shouldn't have to find this out in court.
你們不應該在法庭上知道這一切
Find out what?
知道什麼
Years ago... it was many yes ago...
多年前... 很多年以前...
Your father was engaging in his... his extramarital activities.
你們父親 沉溺在他的婚外戀中
And I had a moment of weakness.
我那時也一時糊塗
I cheated on him.
我背叛了他
With Malcolm Merlyn.
和Malcolm Merlyn
No.
不
No,I...
不可能 我...
I asked you about this.
我問過你
Last year.
就在去年
You said that there was nothing between you two!
你說過你們之間是清白的
There wasn't.
確實沒什麼
Sweetheart,it wasn't an affair.
親愛的 那不是婚外情
It was very brief,and a long time ago.
那只是個插曲 而且已經過去很多年了
And despite it,you remained friends with Mr.Merlyn.
儘管如此 你一直和Merlyn先生保持朋友關係
In fact,he frequently attended parties at your home.
他也確實經常來你家參加宴會
He was my husband's best friend until Malcolm killed him.
直到我丈夫被Malcolm殺了前 他們都是好友
And this is why you claimed to feel as though
所以你聲稱一直覺得
you were in fear for your life and the lives of your children?
你和你孩子的生命一直受到威脅
Well,I think it's a fairly compelling reason.
我覺得這理由很充分
Last year,your second husband,Walter Steel,was abducted by Mr.Merlyn,is that correct?
去年你的第二任丈夫Walter Steel 被Merlyn先生綁架了對吧
Yes.So you seen.
是的 就是那樣
Why didn't Merlyn kill Walter,the same as your first husband?
為什麼Merlyn不像殺了你第一任丈夫那樣 殺了Walter
I convinced Malcolm not to.
我勸說Malcolm別那麼做
And Malcolm listened to you.
Malcolm聽了你的勸
Your friend spared Walter's life,and yet,
你的朋友放過了Walter 而現在
you'd have this jury believing that you and your children were in danger?
你還想讓陪審團相信 你和你孩子的生命受到威脅嗎
- We were.I was afraid...  - Afraid of getting caught.
- 事實如此 我一直害怕... - 害怕被逮捕
Despite whatever youthful mistakes I might have made,Malcolm Merlyn was a dangerous man.
不管我犯過什麼無知的錯 Malcolm Merlyn是個危險人物
To other people.
那只是對別人而言
But the only person who truly posed a danger to Moira Queen and her family was Moira Queen.
唯一對Moira Queen和她家人 造成威脅的就只有Moira Queen
Hey.
你好
Ok,if you want to attack me,go right ahead.
如果你想打我 請便吧
But you should know that you're not going to say anything that I haven't already said to myself.
但你要知道 不必再多說什麼了 我早已罵過自己了
Whoa.
別這樣
I know that that was difficult for you,and I just want to make sure that you're ok.
我知道這對你來說很痛苦 我只是想來確認你還好嗎
No,no.
不 不
I don't understand how you can forgive me after what I just did in there.
我不明白 你怎麼能原諒我剛剛的所作所為
I don't understand how anyone could.
我不明白怎麼有人能做到
So,obviously you three took the Hosen out of this cave.
顯然是你們三個把護身符從洞裡拿走了
Lift him up.
抬他起來
Now I know he doesn't have it,which means one of you two does.
我已經知道護身符不在他身上 那就是在你們其中之一手上
Give it to me,and we'll discuss an exchange.
把它給我 我們來談談交換條件
We don't know what you're talking about.
我們不明白你在說什麼
Give us Oliver,and we'll leave you alone to look for it.
把Oliver放了 就讓你一個人去找
Anybody else want to be stupid?
還有誰腦子壞了嗎
Hey.Hey!Fine.Take 'em.
喂 喂 都退下
Cut him loose.
放了他
What are you doing?!
你幹什麼
We have to keep moving,they're following us!
快跑 他們追來了
Obviously we're continuing to monitor both of these major stories
我們會持續跟進這兩起
in what has become a significant news day here in Starling.
斯特林城頭條新聞事件的動向
What can you tell us about...
如果有最新消息...
Oliver's going to be pretty wrapped up with his mother.
Oliver為他母親忙的脫不開身
You making any process on how The Count's getting Vertigo into people's systems?
你查到伯爵怎麼把迷幻藥注入人體了嗎
Not much.
還沒有
Each dot is the home of somebody with withdrawal symptoms.
圓點顯示的是有戒癮症狀的人的住址
That seems pretty random.
看上去很雜亂
That's because it's very random.
因為確實很雜亂
Ok.
好吧
What if people weren't exposed at home; what if they got dosed at work?
如果人們不是在家裡感染的 是在工作地感染的呢
Can you do this by their employment addresses?
你能查到他們的工作地嗎
I'm really starting to wonder what it would take to impress you guys.
你們的腦筋真的很讓人費解啊
It's a trail.
是條道路
A path through the city.
一條穿越城市的小路
Any place you've been?
你去過這裡某地嗎
59th and Dell,that's where I got my flu shot.
59號大街和戴爾大街 我去接種流感疫苗
You got your vaccination from one of those trucks,right?
你是在某輛卡車上接種的疫苗對嗎
One of those roving flu trucks?
某輛流感疫苗卡車
The route.
路徑圖
It's a flu vaccination tour.
是巡迴疫苗接種計劃
A truck sent out by Starling City Mobile Care.
斯特林城移動醫療隊派出的卡車
I got addicted after one injection?
我在注射後就上癮了嗎
That can happen?
怎麼可能
Sure.Try heroin some time.
沒錯 下次試試海洛因吧
Not try...
別去試...
Try.
還是試吧
All right,where's the truck now?
好吧 卡車現在在哪兒
Downtown.
市中心
What do you think?
你想幹嘛
Call Oliver?
呼叫Oliver嗎
No,no,he's busy with his family.I'll go.
不行 他為家裡的事 忙得焦頭爛額 我自己去
Yeah,no.
好吧 不行
That's not happening.
那可不行
I'll go.
還是我去吧
Felicity,it's too dangerous.
Felicity 這太危險了
It could turn out to be nothing.
有可能只是虛驚一場
If it's not,I'll call.
如果不是 我會呼叫支援
...courtroom drama you've just witnessed?
...剛剛見證了一場法庭劇
Bethany,no one expected the turn that testimony took.
Bethany 沒人期待證詞能帶來逆轉
A revelation that Moira Queen once had an affair with Malcolm Merlyn
Moira Queen 與Malcolm Merlyn的一次風流韻事
became the sole focus of the prosecution's cross.
成了檢控方的關注焦點
Hello?
你好
Anybody home?
有人在嗎
Vertigo.Got ya.
迷幻藥 到手
Funny,eh?
真有趣
You took the words right out of my mouth.
你搶了我的台詞
Thea?
Thea
Can we call it a night?
今天有結果了嗎
Jury just signaled that they could have a verdict.
陪審團剛剛示意說可能要有結論了
Judge will not send them home.
法官不會放他們回家的
He wants to get this over with.
他想今天解決這件事
Line forms behind me.
真是天不助我
A verdict that quickly is bad,isn't it?
越早判決對我們越不利 是嗎
I think the two of you should prepare for the worst.
我想你們最好做好最壞的準備
Excuse me.
失陪一下
Felicity...
Felicity...
Oliver.
Oliver
Is it ok if I call you Oliver?
不介意我叫你Oliver吧
Surprised to hear from me,right?
聽到是我很吃驚嗎
Not as surprised as I was.
我可是比你更驚訝
You see,I find this not unattractive blonde,getting all up in my business.
尤其當我發現這位不性感的金髮女郎 在插手我的大買賣
And what does she have on her?
看看她身上戴著什麼
A Queen Consolidated I.D.badge.
一枚Queen公司的身份牌
Now,I think to myself,why does that name ring a bell?
我就奇怪了 這名字怎麼這麼耳熟
Oliver Queen.
Oliver Queen
He tried to buy off me last year,just before the hood put me in a padded cell.
去年就在帽衫俠把我扔進牢房前 他還想收買我
Ipso facto,Arrow.
事實上該叫你 綠箭俠
Where are you going?!
你要去哪兒
Oh...
我...
Something's come up at the office.
辦公室出了點事
Ollie,the jury!
Ollie 陪審團還在討論
I have to go.
我必須去
Pretty swanky offices.
真是間不錯的辦公室
You can see all the destruction that your mom caused from up here.
從這兒能看見所有你母親破壞的地方
What do you want?
你想要什麼
World peace and personal satisfaction.
世界和平和自我滿足
Though not necessarily in that order.
也可以先滿足我
You poisoned me and put me in a hole.
你給我注射迷幻藥又把我扔進監獄
You have no idea how much I hated you for that.
你不知道我有多恨你
Turns out,someone else hates you,too.
不過 還有個恨你入骨的人
- Who? - Who?Oh,you're going to be surprised when you find out.
- 誰 - 誰 你知道後會嚇一跳的
He's a man of means.
他是個能人
Set me up with my new operation so I could draw you out.
給我安排新的交易 我就能引誘你了
To do what?
引誘我做什麼
This.
這個
You're going to have to try harder.
你得再努努力
Done!
好
Come on!
過來
So now we move on to plan B.
現在要實行備用計劃了
Oliver,don't!Not for me!
Oliver 別管我
Quiet,please.I'm threatening.
安靜點 我要嚇嚇他
Lower your bow.
放下弓
Your problem is with me.
這是咱倆之間的事
It's not with her.
跟她無關
Well,then,consider this your penalty for making me go to plan B in the first place.
這是你讓我實行備用計劃的懲罰
It's all right.You're safe.
沒事了 你安全了
Oh,you were shot.
你中槍了
Hey.It's nothing.
沒事的
Any news?
有新消息嗎
Where have you been?
你去哪了
Something...
Queen集團
happened at Queen Consolidated.
出事了
You will see it on the news later.
一會兒新聞會播
Just don't worry about it.
別擔心了
What would you have done if there'd been a verdict?
要是有裁決了你會怎樣
Thea...
Thea
I don't know.
我不知道
Are you ok?
你沒事吧
Jury's back.
陪審團回來了
Come on.
過來
I have received a note that the jury has arrived at a verdict.
陪審團有了裁決
Please publish the verdict.
請宣讀裁決
In the superior court of Star county state versus Moira Queen verdict...
高級法院斯特郡檢察官 起訴Moira Queen一案 裁決如下
On one count of conspiracy in the first degree,the defendant is found not guilty.
一級同謀罪起訴中 被告人被判無罪
On the 503 counts of murder in the first degree,the defendant is found...
一級謀殺罪起訴中 被告人被判...
Not guilty.
無罪
Mom.
媽
I love you both so much.
我愛你們
A stunning result,as Moira Queen is acquitted of all charges.
意外的結果 Moira Queen無罪釋放
In a day that's provided a week's worth of shocks and legal twists,
今天的新聞堪稱本周法律界震驚之最
many had pronounced this case a done deal.
很多人都以為會判定有罪
Congratulations.
恭喜
Is that appropriate?
這合適嗎
She should have lost.
她本該輸官司的
She should have been convicted.
本該被判有罪的
Did you want her to be?
你希望這樣嗎
I expected her to be.
我希望
Verdict doesn't make sense.
判決不合理啊
Still,your mom must be thrilled.
你媽肯定還是很震驚
Beyond.
震驚死了
It's more like shock,I think.
肯定不止是震驚
They're processing her now.
他們還在起訴她
I just wanted to check in on you.
我只想確認下你沒事吧
And you.
還有你
I'm feeling better.
我好多了
And,with the Vertigo tainted vaccine,
對於受感染的致幻劑疫苗
Queen Consolidated's Applied Sciences Division was able to formulate a non-addictive treatment.
Queen集團的應用科學部門 研究出了誡癮療法
Good.
很好
I need to meet my family at home.
我要回家看看家人
So you guys go home,get rest.
你們也回家休息
- Good night. - Good night.
- 晚安
Oliver.I,uh...
Oliver 我...
- I just wanted to say thank you. - Yeah.
- 我想說謝謝 - 沒事
And I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
For what?
抱歉什麼
I got myself into trouble again,and you...
我又自找麻煩 還害你...
killed him.
殺了他
You killed again,and I am sorry that I was the one to put you in a position where you had to make that kind of choice.
你又殺人了 很抱歉是因為我 你才必須如此選擇
Felicity...
Felicity
He had you,and he was going to hurt you.
他劫持了你 要傷害你
There was no choice to make.
別無選擇
Why did you do that?!
你為什麼這樣做
Because you stopped the captain from killing me.
因為你阻止他殺我
Thank you for coming.
謝謝你來
Shado,he doesn't look too good.
Shado 他不太好
He's not.
是不太好
Who's this?
你是誰
It's complicated.
這很複雜
That Hosen thing they're looking for is back on the plane.
他們又為找那護身符的東西回來了
No,I've got it.
不 我拿到了
It has a Buddhist inscription on one side.
一面是佛教的銘文
It reminded me of my father.
讓我想起我爸
I'm pretty sure they aren't interested in Buddhism.
我相信他們對佛教沒興趣
What's on the other side?
另一面是什麼
Ok,numbers,what...
好吧 是數字
Coordinates.
是坐標
To what?
什麼的坐標
A Kairyu-class Japanese submarine which ran aground here during World War II.
第二次世界大戰在此處擱淺的 一艘日本潛水艇
What do these guys want with a 70 year old sub?
他們要一艘70年前的潛水艇做什麼
The sub isn't important,but what's on it...
潛水艇不是重點 是上面有什麼
It'll save the human race.
能救人類
Will it save him?
能救他嗎
Well,you survived your own stupidity,congratulations.
你沒被自己做的傻事害死 恭喜
You know...
你知道嗎
I needed you to deal with any resistance that I encountered on the island.
我需要你去解決我在島上遇到的居民
I got to say,you've done a fairly lousy job of that.
我必須得說 你這工作做得太差了
Congratulations.
恭喜
You're the new captain.
你是新船長
I arranged for  to take out the Arrow,and all I accomplish is reigniting the vigilante's killing spree.
我讓伯爵去幹掉綠箭俠 而最終只引得他殺欲又起
Sir,there's been a development.
先生 這已經在發展了
Brother Cyrus...
Brother Cyrus
How do you feel?
你感覺如何
Stronger.
更強壯了
Good.
很好
Then you're ready.
那你準備好了
Mrs.Queen,how does it feel to get away with murder?
Queen女士 逃脫法網的感覺如何
Once you go out back,there's a car waiting for you.
你回去後 會有輛車在等你
Did you kill your first husband?
你殺了你第一任丈夫嗎
Just keep going.
繼續走
Obviously Mrs.Queen is overjoyed that the jury has ruled that she was acting under terrible duress.
顯然 Queen女士很開心 陪審團裁決 她的行為是因為監禁而生
Can you give us anything else?
您還能再說幾句嗎
This way,Mrs.Queen.
這邊請 Queen女士
The freeway will be quicker.
走高速會更快
I'm sorry,Mrs.Queen.
抱歉 Queen女士
I was instructed not to take you home.
我被指示不帶你回家
Not yet.
現在不回
Where are we?
那我們在哪
I-I don't know this place.
我不認識這裡
I've got her,sir.
我接到她了 先生
Hello,Moira.
Moira 你好
They said you were dead!
他們說你死了
There are parts of the world where death is an illusion.
在有些地方 死亡只是種幻覺
I've been to one.
我就去過這種地方
I learned to be very convincing.
我學著讓別人以為我死了
But I returned because you needed my help.
但因為你需要我的幫助 我又回來了
Help?
需要幫助
With your trial.
幫助你的審訊
You didn't think that jury acquitted you without a little persuasion?
你不覺得陪審團無罪釋放你 太沒有信服力了嗎
Dear God.
天啊
What do you want,Malcolm?
你想要什麼 Malcolm
I still have resources in Starling.
我在斯特林市還有幫手
Associates.
同伴
Including one in the D.A.'s office.
其中一個人在地方檢察官的辦公室
I followed Mr.Donner's investigation of you with interest.
我關注Donner先生對你的調查
The ease with which you lied about us for years,it made me wonder whether you lied to me .
你從容地跟我們了幾年撒謊 讓我懷疑你是不是也在跟我撒謊
No.No.
沒有
It was a matter of a simple surreptitious genetics test to confirm my suspicion.
一次簡單的秘密基因檢測 就可以證實我的疑慮
Don't.
不要
Imagine my joy at learning that Thea is my daughter.
想像一下我發現Thea是我女兒時的喜悅
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com/bbs=-Sync: YTET-收音机头
-------------------------- 本論壇字幕僅翻譯交流學習之用 禁止任何商業用途否則後果自負 --------------------------
ARROW Season2Episode 02
綠箭俠 第二季 第七集 完